A Guide to the
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Campaign Buttons and Memorabilia
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
7130-g
This collection consists of 30 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Contents List
- U.S. Elections
  - "I Have Seen the Future" ca. 1936
  - "No Royal Family" ca. 1944
  - "Dewey/Warren" 1948
  - "I Like Ike" 1952 and 1956
  - "Let's Back Ike" 1952 and 1956
  - "Ike and Dick" 1952 and 1956
  - "They're for You--Ike Dick" 1952 and 1956
  - "Eisenhower First Voter Nixon-Ives" 1952 and 1956
  - Pin, "Ike" 1952 and 1956
  - "Nixon/Lodge" 1960, 2 buttons
  - "Draft Bill?/Scranton/Sure We Will!" 1964
  - "Goldwater" 1964
  - "Goldwater and Miller" 1964
  - "Goldwater in '64" 1964
- New York Elections
  - "A Great Team-Vote Republican" 1942?
  - "Dulles" ca. 1948
- Virginia Elections
  - Andrews/State Rights Party Virginia/Werdel" post 1948
  - "For Governor J. Lindsay Almond" 1958
  - "Byrd-U.S. Senate" ca. 1960s
  - "Elect Byrd Senator" ca. 1960s
  - "Fred Pollard for Governor" 1969
  - "Spong" ca. 1970
  - "Robinson/Congress" ca. 1976
- Miscellaneous
  - Annual Meeting--Birth Control Federation of America, Inc,. Waldorf Astoria, Jan. 28-30, 1942 1942
  - Virginia Gold Cup Races Member 1959
  - Mount Vernon Place Methodist Church, Washington, D.C. n.d.
  - NFBPWC [National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs] n.d.
  - Uniform button n.d.
  - Miss Joe Wright, Jamestown, Va. n.d.